https://destudio.co/privacy/

Contact
PRIVACY POLICY1. Protecting your privacyThis destudio.co website is owned and operated by Desmond Studio based in Malaysia, which is committed to protecting the information about you that we collect, store and use when you provide it to us at our website.This document describes how we manage any personal information we have collected about you from the website.By accessing our website, you accept the terms and conditions of its use and consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and the terms and conditions of use of the website.If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices or believe that your privacy has been breached, please contact us at our e-mail info@destudio.co and provide details of the incident so that we can investigate it. We request that all complaints be made in writing so that we can be sure about the details of the complaint. We will treat your complaint confidentially, investigate your complaint and aim to ensure that we contact you and your complaint is resolved within a reasonable time.
2. COLLECTION & USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION2.1 What personal information about me does De Studio hold, and how it is collected:User-Submitted ContentThe website allows you to post and submit content and when you do, we collect the information that you submit. If you post any content, pursuant to our terms and conditions of use, you authorize us to publish that content, to publish the name under which you submit the content and you indemnify us in respect of claims or losses resulting from our publication of that content.Geo-Location DataWe may ask to track location-based information from your mobile device while using our website or services we provide, in order to tailor your experience. If you don’t grant permission then we will not collect any location-based data.
2.2 What does De Studio do with my personal information?We collect, hold and use your personal information for a number of purposes, as outlined below:In general, we use the information that we collect to:1. Provide services to you and operate the website;2. Contact you via phone, writing or email in relation to your requests;3. Display, update and maintain the content of the website;4. Tailor your experience of the website and our communications to you; and5. Send information about future events, email communications or newsletters (both electronic and hardcopy) outlining news, services or events.PromotionsIf we collect information from you as part of any promotions, we may use the information that we collect in profiling your use of our services and in promoting our services.General usesWe may also use the information that we collect from you:1. For our internal administrative, marketing and planning requirements;2. To compile and report statistics, with all the relevant personal and/or proprietary information de-identified prior to the completion of such statistics; and3. For purposes that are expressly permitted under any agreement with you, including the terms under which we agree to provide any service to you.
2.3 To whom will De Studio disclose my personal information?We do not disclose contact information about you publicly or to other third parties, unless:it is authorized or required by law (or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us in relation to the website);pursuant to an agreement with you; oras otherwise outlined in this policy.We may display your submitted content regarding your reviews and comments about our partners for whom information can be requested via the website, as part of the website. The website may include functionalities that allow you to control whether or not the public or other users of the website are able to view your user-submitted content. We will use reasonable endeavors to implement your selection.When necessary to provide a service to you, we will also disclose your personal information (on a confidential basis) to educational institutions, training providers and others that we use in the ordinary operation of our business, user experience research and surveys, website hosting and support and maintenance. We will only disclose your information to the extent required for the limited purpose of the third party providing services to you (in the case of participating educational institutions or training providers) or as contracted to us so that we may provide our services.If De Studio is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information or other information may be part of the transferred assets.We may also disclose aggregated data (in a form that does not identify you individually) to our advisors for the purposes of conducting market and user experience analysis.While we store the majority of the personal information that we collect from you in Malaysia, we may from time to time store some of the information in a computer server located in the United States or elsewhere. We will take such steps as are reasonable in the circumstances to ensure that the overseas recipient does not breach the privacy principles.
2.4 TestimonialsWe may publish customer testimonials and contents on our website, in social media profiles, and within advertising creative material. These testimonials may contain personally identifiable information. We will obtain your written consent at the time the testimonial is recorded. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at info@destudio.co.
2.5 Manner of collectionWe will use reasonable endeavors to only collect information directly from you. If you are disclosing details of another person, it is your sole responsibility to ensure that that person understands and consents to the collection, use, and disclosure of their personal information in the manner set out in this policy.
3. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY OUR WEBSITE3.1 Cookie PolicyAs is true of most web sites we and, in some instances, our third-party tracking-utility partners gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track users’ movements around the website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts are used by De Studio and our partners (marketing and development partners), affiliates, or analytics or service providers (online customer support provider, email marketing system). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as an aggregated basis.We use cookies for authentication purposes and to tailor the website to user preferences. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use LSOs such as HTML5 to collect and store information.We use Google Analytics Advertising products: remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Analytics demographics and interest reporting. Google Analytics collects data about our site traffic via Google Advertising Cookies and anonymous identifiers. Data collected via these Google products is not linked with any personally identifiable information you submit while on our website. If you wish to opt-out of the Google Analytics data collection, you may do so on Google’s website.Some components of the website utilize Google Maps mapping services. Your use of Google Maps is subject to Google’s terms of use and Google’s privacy policy and may be amended by Google from time to time.
3.2 AdvertisementsWe may partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner may use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on the website and other websites that you may visit to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.
3.3 Social Media FeaturesThe website may include social media features, such as a like button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.
4. MARKETING MATERIALWe may use your personal information to provide you with material, promotions, and communications from time to time about services and products available to you from us, or from other service providers in partnership with us. This information will only come from us. We will not on-sell your personal information to other providers without your consent. You may opt-out of receiving promotional materials from us at any time by following the ‘unsubscribe’ link on the relevant promotional email.
5. PROTECTING AND MAINTAINING PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe will take all reasonable steps to protect the information we hold about you from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that our systems and stored data will be completely free from third party interception or are free from corruption.Certain parts of the website (such as those parts that require you to provide us with your billing and payment details) provide the ability for you to transmit information to our website in an encrypted form by using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Further, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. In light of this, we cannot ensure or warrant and do not warrant, the security or privacy of your personal information, including payment and account details. You transmit this information at your own risk. If you have any questions regarding security you can contact us at info@destudio.co.You are solely responsible for maintaining the security of your passwords and/or any account information. We will destroy or de-identify your personal information when it is no longer needed or required to be kept by law or to provide services to you. We will also preserve the content of any email or information you submit if we believe we have a legal requirement to do so, or if any form of email abuse is suspected.If you use our website to link to another site, we encourage you to view their terms and conditions of use, privacy policies and security statements before disclosing any of your personal information on those sites.
6. ACCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATIONIt is your responsibility to advise us of any changes to your personal details to ensure we can keep our records accurate and up to date. If you wish to access the information we hold of you, please submit a request at info@destudio.co making the appropriate changes. If you believe that the personal information we hold about you is incorrect, you are entitled to request amendment of such information. If we do not agree that there are grounds for amendment, then we will add a note to the personal information stating that you disagree with it.If you know the information we hold about you is not accurate or complete, please notify us. We will respond to requests for access within 30 days.We will retain your information for as long as your account (if you have one) is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
7. PRIVACY CONCERNSIf you have any concerns about how we handle your personal information or require further information, please contact the Privacy Officer at info@destudio.co. Also use this contact if you no longer consent to receiving marketing material from us, or to the posting of your personal information on the website.
8. CONTACT USCustomer inquiries WhatsApp +6016 6100 400
Effective Date: January 10th, 2020
×
Hello!
Click one of our representatives below to chat on WhatsApp or send us an email to info@destudio.co
Don’t hesitate to message us.
×
<<<
